FILIMON DINGAMO

+17039654153

filasfaw456@gmail.com



Lorton, VA



SUMMARY

A junior-level front-end Web-Developer with a passion for designing, developing, and testing web applications with strong analytical, communication, and problem-solving skills. I am committed to creating websites that meets business requirements and enhances customer experience.

EDUCATION

Northern Virginia Community College

Front-End Web Developer

Associate's Degree in Computer Science 2020 – 2022

George Mason University

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science 2022 – Current

Knowledge Hut Full Stack Javascript Web Developmen Bootcamp

2023 - Current

SKILLS

- **Programming languages:** HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Java, C
- Tools and Technologies: Git, GitHub, React, Bootstrap
- Exceptional communication and interpersonal skills
- Ability to work independently and as part of a team
- Detail-oriented and able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Live Video Production

Addis Lidet Church 2020 - Present

- Coordinated and executed live video shoots at Addis Lidet International Church in Springfield, VA.
- Operated and maintained audio-visual equipment, including microphones, musical instruments, and speakers, to ensure high-quality live video transmissions.
- Collaborated with the production team to implement new ideas and techniques, contributing to the growth and development of the live video production program.

Cashier

Muscle Maker Grill | 2021 - 2022

- Managed Point of Sale (POS) systems and processed customer transactions, demonstrating expertise in handling data input and output processes.
- Maintained a high degree of accuracy in handling financial transactions, reflecting strong attention to detail and problemsolving skills.

PROJECTS

- Random Meme Generator: Generates a random meme image from an API and allows user to add text to the image. (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React).
 - Github: https://github.com/Filimon111/Meme-Generator
- <u>Calculator</u>: A simple calculator that does basic computations. (HTML, CSS, JavaScript).
 - Github: https://github.com/Filimon111/Calculator
- <u>Portfolio Website</u>: A personal portfolio website listing information about me, my projects and skills. (HTML, CSS, JavaScript). Github: https://github.com/Filimon111/Personal-Portfolio

Portfolio: https://filimonspersonalportfolio.netlify.app/Github: https://github.com/Filimon111